Guide to the Miscellaneous human sexuality periodicals,circa 1950-2003
Miscellaneous human sexuality periodicals,circa 1950-2003
- Pride Guide 2005 (The LOFT [The Lesbian and Gay Community Services Center]) (Box 6)
  Publisher: The LOFT (The Lesbian and Gay Community Services Center Inc.)
- Pride of Arizona, The (Box 6)
  Subject: 1970s, Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual, News, Politics, Legal
  Publisher: The Pride Publishing Company
- Pride Source MIchigan (Accessing the Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual and Transgender Community) (Box 6)
  Subject: Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual, Transgender, Community, Directory
  Publisher: Pride Source Corporation
  Publication City: Farmington, MI
- Pride Weekly (Box 6)
  Subject: 1990s, Race, Gender issues, Legal, Politics, News, Alternative local newspaper, Gay, Bisexual, Lesbian, HIV/AIDS
  Publisher: AU Courant, Inc.
- Prime Time Vacations for Men (Box 6)
  Subject: Gay, Travel, Men, 2000s
  Publisher: Prime Time Vacations For Men, Inc.
- Prism, The (Community Alternative News and Views) (Box 6)
  Subject: Alternative local newspaper, News, Legal, Politics, 1990s, Military, Veterans, Health, Medicine
  Publisher: Progressive Newspaper, Inc.
- Prisma News (Box 6)
  Subject: 1980s, College/University, Education, Legal, Gay liberation movement, Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual, HIV/AIDS, Youth
- Privacy Project Update (NGLTF) (Box 6)
  Subject: NGLTF, 1980s, Politics, Legal, Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual, Heterosexual, Gay liberation movement
- project MOVE bulletin (maximizing options in vocational education) (Box 6)
  Subject: Education, College/University, Schools, Gender issues, Anti-sexist men, Men, Occupation Based Organizations
  Publisher: Project MOVE (NYS Education Department), Office of Occupational and Continuing Education
  Publication City: Utica, NY
- Proud of our Past / Looking to the Future (The Official Guide to Lesbian & Gay Pride Weeks in Boston) (Box 6)
  Subject: Pride Parade and Events, 1990s, Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual
  Publisher: The Boston Lesbian & Gay Pride Committee
- Proud Out Loud (New Mexico) (Box 6)
- Provincetown Banner (Box 6)
  Subject: News, Classifieds, Alternative local newspaper, 1990s, Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual, Community, Politics
  Publisher: Provincetown Banner, Inc.
  Publication City: Provincetown, MA
- Provincetown Mirror, The (Box 6)
  Subject: News, Alternative local newspaper, 1980s
- Provincetown Positive (Box 6)
  Subject: HIV/AIDS, Community, Alternative local newspaper, 1990s, Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual, Health, Medicine
  Publisher: Provincetown Positive People With AIDS Coalition
- PRYSM (Providence Youth-Student Movement / "everybody loves gaysians! read all about them!") (Box 6)
  Subject: Asian American, Pacific Islander, Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual, Youth, Schools, Education, Pride Parade and Events, 2000s
  Publisher: PRYSM (Providence Youth-Student Movement)
  Publication City: Providence, RI
- Ptown Scene, The (Box 6)
  Subject: Entertainment, 1990s, Directory, Classifieds, Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual, Transgender, Drag
  Publisher: Ptown Scene, Inc.
- Public Health Update (Box 6)
  Subject: Health, HIV/AIDS, 1980s, Medicine, Politics, Legal
  Publisher: Public Health Foundation (Established by the Association of State and Territorial Health Officials)
- Puce Mongoose, The (Box 6)
  Subject: Women, 1970s, Feminist, Gender issues, Legal, Politics
  Publisher: United Sisters
  Publication City: Garwood, NJ
- Pussy Grazer (Box 6)
  Subject: Zine, Women, Lesbian, Transgender, Transsexual, Drag, Transvestite, Men, Gender Issues, Gay, Queer, 1990s
  Publisher: Sexual Orgasm Productions
- PWA - RAG (Prisoners with AIDS-Rights Advocacy Group) (Box 6)
  Subject: Prisoners, HIV/AIDS, Politics, 1980s, Medicine, Health, Legal
  Publisher: Prisoners With AIDS - Rights Advocacy Group
  Publication City: Milan, MI / Milwauke, WI
- PWGLA: Prince William Gay and Lesbian Association Newsletter (now known as Equality Prince William) (Box 6)
  Subject: Gay liberation movement, Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual, News, Community service, Legal, Politics, 1980s
  Publisher: Prince William Gay and Lesbian Assocication (PWGLA)
  Publication City: Manassas, VA
- Q (Box 7)
  Subject: Entertainment, Queer, Drag, Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual, Leather, Classifieds, 1990s
  Publisher: Q Press
  Publication City: Wilkes-Barre, PA
- Q International (Box 7)
  Subject: Gay male, Gay, 1970s, Preforming arts, Men, Arts, Physique, Travel
  Publisher: Q-Centaur, Ltd.
- Q Magazine (Box 7)
  Subject: Gay, Alternative local newspaper, Queer, News, 1980s
  Publisher: Push Press
  Publication City: Vancouver, BC
- Quash (Newsletter of the Grand Jury Project, Inc.) (Box 7)
  Subject: 1980s, Legal, Politics, News
  Publisher: Grand Jury Project, Inc.
- Queer (German language) (Box 7)
  Subject: Queer, 2000s, Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual, Transgender, Drag, Entertainment, News, Fetish, s/m, Comics
- Queer Exchange, The (A unique offering of lesbian and gay courses for the outragious, artistic, socially conscious and/or mind-probing individual.) (Box 7)
  Subject: Education, 1990s, Directory
  Publisher: The Toronto Centre for Lesbian and Gay Studies
- Queer Muse (Newsletter of the Alliance for Lesbian and Gay Concerns / A professional Interest Committee of The American Association of Museums) (Box 7)
  Subject: History, Archives, Occupation Based Organizations, Education, 1990s, Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual
  Publisher: Alliance for Lesbian and Gay Concerns, The American Association of Museums
- Queer Pages (East Bay Edition 2006) (Box 7)
  Subject: Directory, 2000s, Queer, Community, Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual, Transgender
  Publisher: Eastbay Voice.org
- Query (Tennessee's Lesbian & Gay Newsweekly) (Box 7)
  Subject: 1990s, Lesbian, Gay, Alternative local newspaper, News, Queer, Bisexual, Legal, Politics, Gay liberation movement
  Publication City: Nashville, TN
- Quest Magazine (Box 7)
  Subject: Gay, Men, 1990s, Entertainment, Safer sex, HIV/AIDS, Community
  Publisher: DPBBB Enterprises, Inc.
- R2R (River to River) (Box 7)
  Subject: 1980s, Alternative local newspaper, News, Arts, HIV/AIDS, Gay
  Publisher: R2R, Inc.
- Radiance: A Publication for Large Women (Box 7)
  Subject: Women, People of size, 1980s, Gender issues, Feminist
  Publisher: Radiance
- Radical & Proud (The Newsletter of The National Lesbian and Gay Caucus of The New Alliance Party) (Box 7)
  Subject: Politics, Gay liberation movement, Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual, Legal, 1980s
  Publisher: The National Lesbian and Gay Caucus of The New Alliance Party
- Radical Reviewer, The (Canada's only radical/feminist book review and literary tabloid) (Box 7)
  Subject: Feminist, 1980s, Women, Literary, Gender issues, Lesbian, Heterosexual
  Publisher: The Radical Reviewer
- Rainbow Choices Directory, The (North American Gay & Lesbian Entertainment & Business Directory 1997) (Box 7)
  Subject: Directory, Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual, Transgender, Queer, Community, 1990s, Entertainment, Business
  Publisher: Rainbow Directory, Inc.
- Rainbow Pages of Greater Louisville (A resource for the gay, lesbian and bisexual community) (Box 7)
  Subject: Directory, Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual, 1990s, Queer, Community
  Publisher: Design Publications
- Rainbow Report, The (The Monthly Newsletter of The Society for Senior Gay and Lesbian Citizens) (Box 7)
  Subject: News, Aged, 1980s, Gay, Lesbian, Community
  Publisher: The Society for Senior Gay and Lesbian Citizens
- Rant & Rave (Box 7)
  Subject: Zine, Transgender, Trassexual, Drag, Queer, Gay, Men, HIV/AIDS, Comics
  Publisher: Miss Rant and Miss Rave at the House of Lillian
- Rapping Paper (For and About Gay MidAmerica) (Box 7)
  Subject: 1970s, Gay, Men, Prisoners, Entertainment, News, Alternative local newspaper
  Publisher: Park Lane Associates
  Publication City: Toledo, OH
- RBG: Rehobeth Beach Gayzette (Box 7)
  Publication City: (Rehobeth Beach, DE)
- RCBA (River City Business Association) Newsletter (Box 7)
  Subject: Business, Occupation Based Organizations, 1980s
  Publisher: River City Business Association (RCBA)
- Read This Queers (published anonymously by queers) (Box 7)
  Subject: Queer, Gay liberation movement, Heterosexual, Gender issues, 1990s, History, Politics, Legal
  Publisher: Windy City Times
- Reality Check (This is REALITY CHECK a voice in a world living with HIV and AIDS) (Box 7)
  Subject: HIV/AIDS, 1990s, Medicine, Health, Literary
- Reflect (Box 7)
  Subject: Literary, Women, Gender issues, Feminist, 1970s
- Report to the Community from the San Francisco AIDS/KS Foundation, A (Box 7)
  Subject: HIV/AIDS, Medicine, Health, 1980s
  Publisher: San Francisco AIDS/KS Foundation
- Resource Center Report (Newsletter of the Gay and Lesbian Resource Center) (Box 7)
  Subject: Gay, Lesbian, 1990s, Politics, Legal
  Publisher: The Gay and Lesbian Resource Center
  Publication City: Des Moines, IA
- Resources, Research and Reviews (The "3Rs" Newsletter For Sexuality Educators) (Box 7)
  Subject: Birth control, Contraception, 1980s
  Publisher: Sexuality Education Resources Center
- Response to the Victimization of Women and Children (Journal of the Center for Women and Policy Studies) (Box 7)
  Subject: Women, Women in politics, Women and violent crimes, Anti-violence, Feminist, Families, Parenting, Legal, Politics, 1980s
  Publisher: The Center for Women Policy Studies
- Reverberate (Box 7)
  Subject: Zine, 1990s, Queer, Gay, Lesbian, Community
- Revolution NOW (The Future is Revolution NOW / Souvenir Journal The National Organization for Women) (Box 7)
  Subject: Feminist, Women, Gender issues, 1970s
  Publisher: The National Organization for Women (NOW)
- Reward: True Crime Exposes (Box 7)
  Subject: 1950s, Heterosexual, Entertainment
  Publisher: J.B. Publishing
- Rézo (French language) (Box 7)
  Subject: 1980s, Men, Gay, Entertainment
  Publisher: Imprimerie Nationale
- RSVP Gay Traveller (Box 7)
- Rubyfruit Readher: A Lesbian Communiqué (Box 7)
  Subject: 1970s, Lesbian, Literary, Zine
  Publication City: Felton, CA
- Runes (Sonoma County Women's News Journal) (Box 7)
  Subject: Women, News, 1970s, Women, Literary, Book reviews
  Publication City: Cotati, CA
- S. A. Voice: San Antonio's Christian News & Events Publication article from "Focus on the Family" (Box 7)
  Subject: Religious: Christian
- Sacramento Lesbian & Gay Freedom Fair (Box 7)
  Subject: 1980s, Gay, Lesbian, Pride Parade and Events, Community
  Publisher: Freedom Week Committee (Sacramento)
- San Antonio Community News (Box 7)
  Subject: Gay, Lesbian, News, Alternative local newspaper, 2000s
  Publisher: San Antonio Community News
  Publication City: San Antonio, TX
- San Antonio Unity Yellow Pages (Box 7)
  Subject: Directory, Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual, Community, 1990s
  Publisher: Apex Publishing
- San Francisco Free Press (Box 7)
  Subject: Gay liberation movement, Gay, Lesbian, Alternative local newspaper, Politics, Legal, Bisexual, News, 1960s
  Publisher: San Francisco Free Press
- San Francisco Gazette (Box 7)
  Subject: Gay, Lesbian, Gay liberation movement, Alternative local newspaper, 1970s, News, Community
- San Francisco Review of Books (Out of the Margins / Gay & Lesbian Writing) (Box 7)
  Subject: Book reviews, Gay, Lesbian, Arts, Literary
  Publisher: The San Francisco Review of Books
- San Francisco Spectrum (Box 7)
- San Jose Gay Pride Celebration (free to be...) (Box 7)
  Subject: Pride Parade and Events, Community, 1990s, Drag, Gay, Lesbian
  Publisher: The San Jose Pride Committee
- Sandies (The Academy Awards of San Diego, 1981) (Box 7)
  Subject: Entertainment, 1980s
  Publisher: The Sandies
- Sapling: Gay Youth's Own Newsletter (Box 7)
  Subject: Youth, Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual, 1970s
- Scarlet Letter, The (Produced by and for the Volunteers of the Fund for Human Dignity) (Box 7)
  Subject: Pride Parade and Events, Gay, Lesbian, Legal, Political, 1980s
  Publisher: Volunteers of the Fund for Human Dignity
- Scenes (The Orgy-A Compendium) (Box 7)
  Publisher: Enslow Publishing Corp.
- Screaming Hyena (Not A Straight Book Review) (Box 7)
  Subject: Book review, Gay, Lesbian, 1990s
  Publisher: Palsts Pty. Ltd.
  Publication City: South Yarra
- SCW/WRF News: Souther California Women for the Whitman-Radclyffe Foundation (Box 7)
  Subject: Women, Lesbian, Community, 1970s, Parenting, Families, Gender issues
  Publisher: Southern California Women For The Whitman-Radclyffe Foundation (SCW/WRF)
  Publication City: Studio City, CA
- SDVA Newsletter (San Diego Veterans Association) (Box 7)
  Subject: Veterans, Military, 1990s, Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual
  Publisher: San Diego Veterans Association
- Sea-gull, The (..."Moving On"...) (Box 7)
  Subject: Entertainment, Gay, Lesbian
  Publication City: Atlantic City, NJ
- Searchlight (A Publication of Search Alliance) (Box 7)
  Subject: HIV/AIDS, News, Medicine, Health, 1990s
  Publisher: SEARCH Alliance
- Second Class, Working Class (Box 7)
  Subject: Women, Literary, Gender issues, Politics, Legal, 1970s
- Seed (Box 7)
  Subject: Gay, Lesbian, Political, Legal, Gay liberation movement
- Sensuous Closet Drawings of A.B. (Box 7)
  Subject: Erotica, Arts
- Sexual Health Reports (Box 7)
  Subject: Health, HIV/AIDS, Gay, Medicine, 1980s, Legal, Political
  Publisher: National Coalition of Gay Sexually Transmitted Disease Services (NCGSTDS)
- Sexual Minority Prisoners Caucus (Washington State Reformatory) (Box 7)
  Subject: Prisoners, Gay, Lesbian, 1980s, Legal, Political
  Publisher: Sexual Minority Prisoners Caucus, Washington State Reformatory
  Publication City: Monroe, VA
- Sexuality Library, The (Box 7)
  Subject: Catalog, Erotica, 1990s, Men, Women, Masturbation, Heterosexual, Gay, Lesbian
  Publisher: The Sexuality Library
- Sexually Transmitted Diseases (Abstracts & Bibliography) (Box 7)
  Subject: Health, Medicine, Safer sex, Contraception, Men, Women, Heterosexual, Government Publication(s), 1970s
  Publisher: U.S. Department of Health, Education, and Welfare; Public Health Service; CDC
- SGC Newsletter (Sociologists' Gay Caucus) (Box 7)
  Subject: Education, College/University, Occupation Based Organizations, Gay, Lesbian, 1980s
  Publisher: Sociologists' Gay Caucus
- SheBiz (Directory and Commentary of Women In Business) (Box 7)
  Subject: Women, Business, 1980s, Gender issues, Directory
  Publisher: SheBiz
  Publication City: St. Albans, NY
- Shout! (Box 7)
  Subject: Entertainment, Gay, Lesbian, 2000s
  Publisher: PTM Enterprises, Inc.
- SIDAMonde (French language) (Box 7)
  Publication Country: France
  Publication City: Paris
- SIECUS Dispatch (A Publication for SIECUS [Sex Information and Education Council of teh US]) (Box 7)
  Subject: Education, Safer sex, Contraception, 1980s
  Publisher: SIECUS (Sex Information and Education Council of the US)
- Sin Bros. (Box 7)
  Subject: Gay, Men, Entertainment, Fetish, Drag, Arts, Cruising, Erotica, 1990s
  Publisher: D. Rex Tor
  Publication City: North Hollywood, CA
- Siouxland AIDS Coalition Newsletter (Box 7)
  Subject: HIV/AIDS, 1990s, Community, Health, Medicine
  Publisher: Siouxland HIV/AIDS Coalition
  Publication City: Sioux City, IA
- Slant, The (of the gay, lesbian, bisexual, and transgender communities of the bay area) (Box 7)
  Subject: Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual, Transgender, News, Entertainment, 2000s, Community
  Publisher: The Marin Stonewall Alliance
  Publication City: Corte Madera, CA
- Slippery When Wet (Bisexual. Penetration-positive. Queer) (Box 7)
  Subject: Bisexual, Entertainment, Queer, Erotica, Sexual libertaion, 1990s
  Publisher: More! Productions
  Publication City: Berkeley, CA
- SLS (Schwul Lesbische Studien Bremen) (German language) (Box 7)
  Subject: Lesbian, 1990s, Book reviews, Books
  Publication City: Bremen
- Slut Mag (Box 7)
  Subject: Zine, Women, Gender issues, Entertainment, 1990s
  Publisher: Slut Mag Press
- Snippets: A Mélange of Women (University Heights Ohio) (Box 7)
  Subject: Literary, Gender issues, Parenting, Women, Poetry, 1980s
  Publisher: The Pin Prick Press
  Publication City: University Heights, OH
- Society for the Scientific Study of Sex, Inc., The (The Society Newsletter) (Box 7)
  Subject: Education, College/University, Occupation Based Organizations, Health, Medicine, University of Pennsylvania, 1980s
  Publisher: The Society for the Scientific Study of Sex, Inc. (SSSS)
- Sodomite Invasion, The (Box 7)
  Subject: Gay, Literary, Men, Cruising, Education, College/University, 1990s
  Publisher: College Printers
- SoMo News Connection, The (Box 7)
  Subject: News, Gay, Bisexual, 1990s, Community, News, Political, Legal
  Publication City: Tecumseh, MO
- Soup (translation in process) (Box 7)
  Subject: Literary, Gay, Lesbian, Poetry, 1980s
  Publisher: Howard Quinn Printing
- Source, The: The Ultimate Gay Community Directory (Box 7)
  Subject: Directory, Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual, Transgender, 1990s, Community
  Publisher: Three Dollar Bill, Inc.
- Southern Advocate (Box 7)
  Subject: 1980s, Politics, Legal, Gay liberation movement
  Publisher: Equal Rights Congress, Southern Region
- Southern Comfort (Box 7)
  Subject: Gay, Erotica
  Publisher: HOT! Publishing Company
- Southern Political Report (Box 7)
  Subject: Politics, Legal, 1980s
  Publisher: Hastings Wyman, Jr.
- Spank (A Press for the Rest of Us) (Box 7)
  Subject: 1990s, Drag, Entertainment, Alternative local newspaper
- Spirit of the Androgyne (Box 7)
  Subject: 1970s, Transgender, Gender, Gender issues, Religious, Religious: Spiritual, Religious: Church of the Androgyne, Religious: Chirstian
  Publisher: Church of the Androgyne
- Spoke Space (Box 7)
- SpokeSpace (Newsletter of Hibbs Gallery of Visual and Arts Center) (Box 7)
  Subject: Visual arts, 1980s, Gay arts
  Publisher: The Hibbs Gallery and Visual Arts Center
- Squirt (Box 7)
  Subject: Entertainment, 1990s, Pride Parade and Events, News, Alternative local newspaper
  Publisher: OutWeek Publishing Corp.
- Staff Notes (newsletter for the staff of Seattle Gay Clinic) (Box 7)
- Star Dist: News from the Saint (Box 7)
- Star Dust: News from the Saint (Box 7)
  Subject: Entertainment, Military, 1980s, Alternative local newspaper
- STEAMagazine (Straight Answers for Gay Guys) (Box 7)
  Subject: Gay male, Cruising, 1970s
  Publisher: Club Bath Chain Association (CBC)
- Summer in the City: Guide to Atlanta (Box 7)
  Subject: Directory, Pride Parade and Events, Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual, 1990s
  Publisher: Southern Voice
- Suncoast Community Voice (Box 7)
  Subject: 2000s, Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual, News, Community, Transgender
  Publisher: Momentum Publishing
  Publication City: Sarasota, FL
- Swerve (Box 7)
  Subject: Gay, Lesbian, Gay, Alternative local newspaper, 1990s
  Publisher: SWERVE
- Swing San Diego (Box 7)
  Subject: Directory, Cruising, Swingers, 1980s
  Publisher: Dawn Media
- Swing the Pussy (STP) (Box 7)
  Subject: Lesbian, Queer, Women, Feminist, 1990s
  Publisher: STP (Swing The Pussy)
  Publication Country: New York
- Swingers Behind Bars (America's First Pubolication for Liberated Men and Women in Prison) (Box 7)
  Subject: Erotica, Heterosexual, Swingers, Prisoners
  Publication City: East Hartford, CT
- Sydney Gay Guide (1981) (Box 7)
  Subject: Directory, Gay, Alternative local newspaper, 1980s
  Publisher: Gay Society of teh University of New South Wales
- T.A.: Technical Assistance Newsletter (Box 8)
  Publisher: National Minority AIDS Council
- Taiwan Awakening (Box 8)
  Publication Country: Taiwan
  Publication City: Taipei
- Take Action! Networking Calender (Box 8)
  Publisher: Oregon PeaceWorks- Eugene Chapter
  Publication City: Eugene, OR
- Tantra (Box 8)
  Publication City: Torreon, NM
- Technical Assistance Reports (United States Conference of Mayors AIDS/HIV Program) (Box 8)
- Ted: reports from the gay nation (Box 8)
- Teen Fag (Box 8)
  Subject: Gay youth, Entertainment, Comics, Zine, Youth, Gay, Gay male
- Telaraña, La (Box 8)
  Subject: Latina, Latino, Lesbian, Arts, Literary
  Publisher: Tatiana de la Tierra
  Publication City: El Paso, TX
- TEMA International (Box 8)
  Subject: Gay, Lesbian, Gay liberation movement, 1990s, Politics, Legal
  Publisher: The International Gay and Lesbian Human Rights Commission
- Tennessee Gay & Lesbian Coalition Newsletter (Box 8)
- Terrescope (Box 8)
  Publication City: Terre Haute, IN
- Texas NOW Times (Box 8)
  Subject: Feminist, Women
  Publication City: Arlington, Texas
- Texas Women's Political Times (Box 8)
  Subject: Politics, Women
- "That All May Freely Serve" Newsletter (Box 8)
  Subject: Religious, Religious: Christian
- Timarcus Studio Drawings (Box 8)
  Subject: Native Americans, Arts
- Timely Gay Bar Guide (Box 8)
  Subject: Directory, Gay, Gay male, 1970s
  Publication City: Long Island, NY
- Time's Up! (Box 8)
  Subject: NGLTF, 1970s, Pride Parade and Events
- Together Gay (Box 8)
  Subject: Literary, Zine
- TOHR Reporter (Tulsa Oklahomans for Human Rights) (Box 8)
  Subject: 1980s, Gay liberation movement, Politics, Legal
  Publisher: Tulsa Oklahomans for Human Rights
  Publication City: Tulsa, OK
- Tommy's Connection: The New England Travelers Paper (Box 8)
  Subject: Travel, Gay, Alternative local newspaper
- Tomorrow: MSU Gay Group (Box 8)
  Subject: College/University, Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual, 1970s
  Publisher: MSU Gay Group (Minnesota State University)
  Publication City: Mankato, MN
- Too Hot to Handle (Box 8)
  Subject: 1980s, Classifieds, Cruising, Gay male
- Too, Too Queer Monitor (Triangle Artists Group) (Box 8)
  Subject: Gay, Humor, News
- Torch, The (News and Information for Gay People in Fort Wayne) (Box 8)
  Subject: News, Alternative local newspaper, Gay, 1980s
  Publisher: Fort Wayne Lambda Projects, Inc.
  Publication City: Fort Wayne, IN
- Toronto People With AIDS Foundation Newsletter (Box 8)
  Subject: HIV/AIDS, 2000s
  Publisher: Toronto People with AIDS Foundation
- Toronto Rag (Box 8)
  Subject: Arts, Literary, Zine
- Toronto Sports & Cultural Centre Magazine (Box 8)
  Subject: Sports, Gay, Lesbian, Drag
  Publisher: Toronto Sports & Cultural Centre, Inc.
- tpan NOW (Test Positive Aware Network: Empowering, Supporting, Continuing Our Commitment) (Box 8)
  Subject: HIV/AIDS, Health, 1990s
  Publisher: TPAN (Test Positive Aware Network)
- Trans Action: Social Science and Modern Society (Box 8)
  Subject: Politics, Legal, 1970s
  Publisher: Transaction, Inc.
  Publication City: Fulton, MO
- Transperience Daily Bugle (Box 8)
  Subject: News, 1970s, Alternative local newspaper
- Travel News from Remote Possibilities (Box 8)
  Subject: Travel, Gay, Lesbian, 1990s
  Publisher: Remote Possibilities
  Publication City: Wailuku, HI
- Traveling America (Box 8)
  Subject: Travel, Gay male, Zine
  Publication City: Fontanelle, IA
- Triangle Business & Professional Guild News (Box 8)
  Subject: Gay, Business, Occupation Based Organizations, Lesbian, News, 2000s
  Publisher: Triangle Business and Professional Guild (TBPG)
- Triangle Community Digest (Box 8)
  Subject: News, Entertainment, Alternative local newspaper, 1980s
  Publisher: Triangle Community Digest Publishing
- Triangle Rag (For and About Lesbians and Bisexual Women of Color Living and Loving in the South) (Box 8)
  Subject: Women of color, Lesbian, Gay liberation movement, 1990s, Alternative local newspaper
  Publisher: Triangle Rag
- Triangle Rising (Arkansas Gay & Lesbian Task Force) (Box 8)
  Subject: Gay, Lesbian, Gay liberation movement, Politics, Legal, Alternative local newspaper
  Publisher: Arkansas Gay & Lesbian Task Force
- Triangle, The (Carrollton's Gay Community Newsletter) (Box 8)
  Subject: Community, News, 1990s, Alternative local newsppaer, HIV/AIDS, Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual
  Publisher: The Triangle
  Publication City: Carrollton, GA
- Triangle, The (The Monthly Newspaper from Gay & Lesbian Community Services of Central Florida, Inc. Serving Orlando's Lesbian, Gay and Bisexual Community) (Box 8)
  Subject: Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual, Alternative local newspaper, News, Politics, Law
  Publisher: Gay & Lesbian Community Services of Central Florida